Personal brand teaching traveling around the world
I always say the same thing to people.
It's not who you know,
is the one who knows you.
Today I can open up many opportunities,
not only because of the personal brand I have,
but sometimes I don't have the contact with the person.
That person has seen me,
has seen my personal brand,
someone has told him about her.
And when we talk about it being a personal brand,
the most basic definition
personal mark is how you present yourself,
but also how they perceive you.
Many people work hard in biography.
perfect.
I am number one,
I am the leader
and that can often even be left in front or not.
There is evidence to support this.
However,
the perception
is what they say about you when you are not in the room.
How do people describe you too?
So I, for example,
when I ask people how
describe Vilma's personal brand,
they say inside,
a duer visionary,
but also dress for success,
which is a movement that I began to promote
several years ago,
is that I dress to remind myself of my worth as well,
my self-esteem,
you understand me,
feel safe
and today this is part of my differentiation strategy.
Because let's be honest,
he who knows how to differentiate himself need not introduce himself
and the best way to differentiate yourself
you know what your story is,
your progress.
You and I can do exactly the same.
Imagine that we are leaders in marketing business.
However,
my life story has nothing to do with yours.
The way in which I have progressed
has nothing to do with yours.
There is a methodology that I like to share
which is about how to create an invincible personal brand.
But that's really something I want to share with you.
If you join the vanguard
somit our face-to-face event at Florida 22,
October 23 and 24.
And don't worry,
if you don't want to travel,
you can buy your virtual ticket.
It is an event where we will gather creativity
with intelligence
artificial to help you in leadership,
business,
marketing and sales.
See you at the forefront!